<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cleyton Farias</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cleyton Farias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World!!! My name is Cleyton and I&amp;rsquo;m a Data Scientist and Ph.D. Candidate in Economics at Universidade Federal de Pernambuco here in Brazil.
I&amp;rsquo;m very passionate about technologies, computers and data. I spend most my time in front of my computer working on a dataset or learning coding instead of studying for exams (kkkkkkk).
My main interests relies on data analysis, specially machine learnign, big data, and econometrics.
Thanks for stepping by!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Julia for Data Science</title>
      <link>/posts/using-julia-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/using-julia-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>This a quick introduction to the Julia programming language and will be presented to you how you can work rightaway with datasets with Julia.
Why Julia? Julia is a high level programming language released in 2012 by a team of MIT researchers. Since its beginning, the aim was to solve the so called two-language programing problem: easy to use functionalities of interpretable languages (Python, R, Matlab) vs high performance of compiled languages (C, C++, Fortran).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/research/</guid>
      <description> Work in Progress “Let there be more light: The impact of headlamp law on road accidents.”, with Leonardo Melo, Giuseppe Trevisan and Breno Sampaio. Work in Progress, January 2019.
 “Commodity prices and business cycles in emerging economies: The role of news shocks”, with Marcelo Eduardo A. da Silva. Working Paper, July 2017.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/vitae/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/vitae/</guid>
      <description> -- Alternative text - include a link to the PDF!
-- -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description> Presentations “Commodity prices and business cycles in emerging economies: The role of news shocks”, presented at: The 39th Annual Brazilian Econometric Society Meeting 2017; The 22nd Annual LACEA Meeting 2017.   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>